邪恶力量前情提要
Previously on Supernatural.
那晚发生的事
What happened that night
赶快带你弟弟出去
Take your brother outside as fast as you can!
快 迪恩 快跑
Now, Dean! Go!
他们亲眼目睹
What they witnessed
玛丽 不
Mary! No!
两兄弟
Sent two brothers
爸爸已经踏上了捕猎之旅
Dad is on a hunting trip...
他好几天没回家了
and he hasn't been home in a few days.
从此踏上征途 22年后
On a quest for answers. 22 years later
我发过誓我再也不猎魔了
I swore I was done hunting.
我一个人不行
I can't do this alone.
不
No!
我们有活儿干了
We've got work to do.
这是老爸最珍贵的财产
This is dad's single, most valuable possession
他所有知道的关于恶魔的东西都记载在这里面
Everything he knows about every evil thing, it is in here.
我觉得他想让我们继续他的工作
I think he wants us to pick up where he left off.
你知道 拯救人类 猎杀恶魔
You know, saving people, hunting things.
家族事业
Family business.
不 我得找出杀杰西卡的凶手
No. I gotta find Jessica's killer.
这是我现在唯一想做的事
This is the only thing I can think about.
萨姆 你知道我们会找到爸爸的 是吧
Sam, you know that we're gonna find dad, yeah?
是的 我知道
Yeah, I know.
《邪恶力量》
怕坐飞机
Nervous flyer?
很明显哈
Is it that obvious, huh?
你知道死于空难的概率多大吗
You know what are the odds of dying in a plane crash?
两万分之一
I mean what, twenty thousands to one?
真让我安心了 谢谢
Oh, it's really reassuring, thank you.
谢谢
Thanks.
阿曼达 你今天怎样
Amanda, how are you today?
挺好的 查克
I'm doing just fine, Chuck.
欢迎登机
Welcome aboard.
15排c座 就在机尾右侧
15-C towards the back of the plane on the right.
祝您旅途愉快 先生
Have a nice flight, sir.
希望如此
Oh, I'm counting on it.
11排f座 在机舱中央
11-F, that's at the middle of the plane on...
谢谢你
Thank you.
左侧
the left.
打扰一下 飞机起飞多久了
Excuse me. Do you know how long we have been up?
大概40分钟
About forty minutes.
时间如飞啊
Wow! Time really does fly, huh?
对不起 我伸展一下筋骨
Excuse me. I've got to stretch my legs.
你该死的在干嘛
Hey, what the hell are you doing?!
天哪
Oh, my god!
早安 宝贝
Morning, sunshine!
几点了
What time is it?
大概5 45
Oh, it's about 5:45.
- 现在是早上 - 是的
- In the morning? - Yap.
今天干什么
Where does the day go?
昨晚你睡着了吗
Did you get any sleep last night?
- 是的 睡了几小时 - 骗人
- Yeah, I got a couple of hours. - You liar.
我三点醒了
See, I was up at 3,
你正在看乔治·福尔曼资讯式广告
And you were watching George Foreman informercials.
我能说什么呢 蛮好看的
What can I say? Riveting TV!
你最后一次睡安稳觉是什么时候
When's the last time you got a good night sleep?
不记得了 不久前吧 这无关紧要
I don't know. A little while I guess. It's not a big deal.
是啊
Yeah, it is!
好吧 感激你的关心
Okay, I appreciate your concern...
我才不关心你呢
Oh, I'm not concerned about you.
你的工作是保护我 所以精神点
It's your job to keep my ass alive! So I need you sharp.
老实说 你还在做关于杰西的噩梦
Seriously you're still having nightmares about Jess?
是啊
Yeah.
但不只是她 而是所有一切
But it's not just her, it's everything.
可能我忘了 这种工作缠上我了
I just forgot, you know, this job... man, it gets to you.
你不能任由这样 你不能让它占据你生活
Well you can't let it. You can't bring it home like that.
那这些东西从来没有让你在晚上惊醒吗
So what? All this it never keeps you up at night?
从不 你从不害怕
Never?! You never afraid?
不怕 真的不怕
No, not really.
这不是害怕
That's not fear.
这是警惕
That's precaution.
好吧 随你怎么说 懒得和你争辩
All right, whatever. I'm too tired to argue.
- 你好 - 迪恩
- Hallo? - Dean?
我是 杰瑞·潘诺斯基
It's huh... It's Jerry Panowski.
你和你的父亲几年前帮过我
You and your dad helped me out a couple of years back.
是的
Oh, right.
宾夕法尼亚的科特宁镇 那个恶作剧鬼
Yeah, up in Kittanning, Pensylvania. The poltergeist thing.
- 它不会又回来了吧 - 没有
- It's not back, is it? - No.
没有
No.
谢天谢地 没有
Thank God, no.
是其它的东西 我觉得可能更严重
But it's something else and I think it could be a lot worse.
是什么
What is it?
我们可以面谈吗
Can we talk in person?
谢谢你们这么快赶来
Thanks for making the trip so quick.
我应该帮助你们 不是让你们帮我
I ought to be doing you guys a favour, not the other way around.
迪恩和你爸真帮了我大忙
Dean and your dad really helped me out.
是的 他告诉过我 是个恶作剧鬼
Yeah, he told me. It was a poltergeist?
《鬼驱人》 伙计 我喜欢那部电影
Poltergeist? Man, I loved that movie.
没人和你说话 走你的路吧
Hey, nobody is talking to you, keep walking.
那个该死的恶作剧鬼
Damn right it was a
几乎拆了我家
poltergeist practically it tore our house apart.
我告诉你
I'll tell you something.
要是没你和你爸 我可能早就挂了
If it wasn't for you and your dad I probably wouldn't be alive.
你爸爸提到过你要去上大学 是吗
Your dad said you are off to college, that's right?
曾经是的 我现在休假
Yeah, I was. I'm... taking some time off.
我敢说 他真为你感到自豪
He was really proud of you, I could tell.
他总是说到你
He talked about you all the time.
- 是吗 - 是的 他真是这样的
- He did? - Yeah, you bet he did.
我试着联系他 但是不行
Oh, hey, you know I tried to get hold of him but I couldn't.
他现在怎样
How is he doing anyway?
他 现在忙于工作
He is... wrapped up in a job right now.
怀念老家伙的同时 萨姆来了
Well, we're missing the old man, we get a Sam.
平等交易 是吧
Even trade, huh?
不 绝不是啊
No, not by a long shot.
有些东西让你们听听
I've got something I want you guys to hear.
我听过这个
I listened to this.
听起来好像出现过
Well, sounded like it was appear on?
常理来说 我没办法拿到这个
Normally, I wouldn't have access to this.
这是驾驶室录音
It's the cockpit voice
美国不列颠航空公司2485航班的
recorder for the United Britannian flight 2485.
我们公司的飞机
It was one of ours.
求救 求救 重复求救
Mayday! Mayday! Repeat!
这是美国不列颠航空2485航班
It's the United Britannian flight 2485...
我们需要你们立即给予指示 我们需要帮助
We wants you to give immediately instructions. We need help...
美国不列颠2485航班 我们收到求救
United Britannian Flight 2485, we copy your mayday.
也许我们有机械故障
maybe we are experiencing some... mechanical failure...
从这起飞 坠毁在大概往南200英里处
Took off from here... crashed about two hundred miles up.
现在他们说是机械失灵
Now they'er saying mechanical failure.
某种原因导致机仓减压 没人知道为什么
Cabin depressurized somehow, nobody knows why.
机上有超过100人 只有7人幸存
Over a hundred people onboard, only seven we got alive.
其中一个是驾驶员
The pilot was one.
他叫查克·兰博特 他是我的好友
His name is Chuck Lambert, he is a good friend of mine.
查克是个
Chuck is a...
他无法承受此事 认为是自己的错
Well, he's pretty broken up about it. Like it was his fault.
- 你认为不是 - 是 我认为不是
- You don't think it was? - No, I don't.
杰瑞 我们要乘客名单
Jerry, we're gonna need passenger manifests,
和幸存者名单
A list of the survivors...
对了 我们要看看飞机残骸
Right, and a... We'll need take a look at the wreckage.
其它的资料没问题 但是飞机残骸
The other stuff is no problem, but the wreckage...
全国安全运输委员会的人把它锁在了证物库里
Fellows in NTSB has it lockdown in an evidence warehouse.
我进不去
No way I've got that clearance.
不要紧
No problem.
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey! - Hi.
怎么呆了那么久
You have been there forever.
想要完美就不能急
You can't rush perfection!
国土安全局
Homeland security?
这可是违法的 甚至对我们来说
It's pretty illegal. Even for us.
是吗 这是新的
Hell, well? Something new.
你知道 别人可不会注意它
You know, people have seen it a thousand times.
那你查到什么了
All right, so what you got?
驾驶室录音里有超自然电子异象
Well, there is definitely EVP on the cockpit voice recorder.
- 是吗 - 听
- Yeah? - Listen.
无人幸存
No survivors!
No survivors?
什么意思 有7个幸存者啊
What's that supposed to mean? There were seven survivors.
难倒我了
Got me.
你怎么认为 闹鬼的飞机
So what you think? A haunted flight?
有很多关于飞机和轮船的幽灵和死亡预兆
There is long history of spirits and death omens
像是幻影旅者
on planes, on ships like phantom travelers.
你还记得401航班吗
Or, do you remember flight 401?
是的 那架失事的飞机
Right, the one that crasher,
航空公司把它的一些部件装到了其它飞机上
and the airlines salvaged some of its parts put in other planes.
驾驶员和副驾驶员的鬼魂缠上了那些部件
And the spirits of the pilot and co-pilot haunted those parts.
- 是的 - 是啊
- Right. - Yeah?
也许我们遇到了相同的情况
Maybe we've similar deal.
那么这些幸存者 你想先和谁谈谈呢
All right, so the survivors. Which one we have to talk to first?
名单上的第三个 马克思·杰夫
Third on the list. Max Jaffe.
为什么是他
Why him?
第一 他住在这附近
For one, he lives around here...
第二 如果有人看到怪异的东西 就是他
and two, if anyone saw anything weird, he did.
为什么这么说
What makes you say that?
我和他妈妈聊过
Oh, I spoke to his mother,
她告诉我去哪找他
and she told me where we find him.
(瑞福特精神病院)
我不明白 我已经和国土安全局谈过了
I don't understand. I already spoke with homeland security.
是的
Right.
有新的信息出现
As new information has come up,
所以你能回答几个问题吗
so if you could just answer a couple of questions.
就在飞机下落前 你注意到有异常吗
Just before the plain went down, did you notice anything unusual?
比如说
Like what?
奇怪的光 也许是诡异的噪音
Strange lights, weird noises maybe?
声音之类的
Voices?
没 什么都没有
No, nothing.
杰夫先生
Mister Jaffe...
- 杰夫 - 杰夫
- Jaffee. - Jaffee...
你自己要求住进来的 是吧
You checked yourself in here, right?
我能问问是为什么吗
Can I ask why?
我有点焦虑不安 从一次坠机事件中生还
I was a little stressed, I survived a plain crash.
什么吓到你了 就是说你怕的是什么
And that's what terrified you? And that's what you afraid of?
我再也不想谈这个了
I... I don't wanna talk about this anymore.
我觉得也许你在飞机上看见了什么
I think maybe you did see something up there.
我们要知道你看见了什么
We need to know what.
不不 只是我的幻觉
No. No, I was delusional.
看到一些东西
Seeing things.
他看到了一些东西
He seeing things.
没事的
It's okay.
请你告诉我们 你觉得自己看见了什么
Then just tell us what you thought you saw, please.
飞机上有个人
There was this man.
他的眼睛
And... he had these... eyes.
是
These...
黑色的
black eyes.
我看见他
I saw him...
我觉得我看见他
I thought I saw him...
怎么啦
What?
他打开紧急出口
He opened the emergency exit.
那是不可能的 是吧 我查过资料
And that's... that's impossible. Right? I mean, I looked that up.
那门上几乎有2吨的压力
There is something like two tons of pressure on that door.
是的
Yeah.
这个人 是不是突然出现又突然消失
This man, uh, did he seemed to appear and disappear?
很快 就像幻影一样
Rapidly, he would looked something like a mirage?
你是疯子吗
What are you, nuts?!
他是个乘客 就坐我前面
He was a passanger, he was sitting right in front of me.
我们到了
So here we are.
乔治·菲尔浦斯 20排C座的乘客
George Phelps. Seat 20-C.
我不管你有多强壮
Hm. Man, I don't care how strong you are.
即使你嗑了药
Even you hopped up on PCP or something...
也不可能在飞机飞行中打开紧急出口门
No way you can open up an emergency door during the flight.
要是人类就不行
No, if you're a human.
也许这个家伙 乔治 是别的什么东西
But maybe this guy, George, is something else.
披着人形外衣的生物
Some kind of a creature maybe, in human form?
那你看这像是那种生物的巢穴吗
Is this look like where a creature's lair to you?
这是你的前夫
This is your late husband?
是的 这就是我的乔治
Yes, that was my George.
你说他是个 牙医
And you said, he was a... dentist?
他飞去丹佛参加一个会议
He was headed to a convention in Denver.
你知道他很怕坐飞机吗
Do you know, that he was petrified to fly?
对他来说那样出行
For him to go like that.
你们结婚多久了
How long have you been married?
13年
13 years.
这些年里
And all that time, did
你有没有注意到他的奇怪举止
you ever noticed anything strange about him?
任何不正常的事情
Anything out of ordinary?
有
Well...
他有胃酸倒流 这是你们指的吗
He had acid reflux, if that's what you mean?
谈话毫无结果 没有意义
I mean it goes without saying it's doesn't make any sense.
一个患有胃溃疡的中年牙医
A middle-aged dentist with
不是那种邪恶人格的人
an ulcers is not exactly evil-personified.
你知道我们要做的就是
You know what we need to do is getting inside
进入运输委员会的仓库 检查残骸
the NTSB warehouse check out the wreckage.
好吧
Okay.
但我们要那么做 最好乔装一下
But if we're gonna go down around, we better look depart.
伙计 我看上去就像《福禄双霸天》的男主
Man, I look like one of the "Blues Brothers".
不 你不像
No, you don't.
你更像第一次参加舞会的七年级生
You look more like a seventh grader at his first dance.
我讨厌这样
I hate this thing.
你还想不想混进仓库呀
Hey, you want to go in that warehouse or not?
那是什么
What is that?
这是个电磁场探测仪
It's an EMF meter.
它可以探测电磁频率
It metes electromagnetic frequencies.
迪恩 我知道电磁场探测仪是什么
Dean, I know what an EMF meter is,
但是为什么这个看上去像个烂随身听
but why is that it looks like as a busted up walkman?
这是我做的 纯手工哟
That's why I made it out of. It's homamade.
是啊 看得出来
Yeah, I can see that.
检查下紧急出口的门把手
Check out the emergency door handle.
- 这是什么 - 让我们查明这个
- What is this stuff? - We are going to find out.
先生们
Gentlemen.
国土安全局
Homeland security?
怎么啦 一对还不够吗
Why? One of you two guys isn't enough?
你说什么
What are you talking about?
你们的两个人5分钟前进去了
Two of your budies went inside not 5 minutes ago.
这身衣服真碍事
Well, these Mort's suits do come in handy.
听着 查克 重新振作起来
Listen, Chuck. Let's get back on the horse.
只是这次 是个小双引擎
Only in this case, it's a little twin engine.
不是个大飞机 是个小飞机
Not even a horse, more like a pony.
我也会陪着你的
And I'll be right there with you, too.
你什么时候不想驾驶了 我来开
Anytime you feel you don't want the wheel, I'll take over.
听着 查克 今天你不是非得这样做
Look, Chuck. You don't have to do this today.
我不想逼你
I'm not try to rush you.
不 等待让我感觉更难受
No... the waiting is worse.
好吧 他们加满油了 出发
Okay, they fueled up the tank. There we go.
这个东西上面覆盖了硫磺
This stuff is covered in sulphur.
你确定
You sure?
你自己看看
Take a look for yourself.
请原谅 我要解雇那个蠢蛋
If you fellas would excuse me, I have an idiot to fire.
爱因斯坦 就是你
Hey, Einstein! Hey, you!
你到底在干嘛 放下扳手
What the hell you doing?! Put the wrench down!
这里没有留下
Yeah, there is not too many things
太多的硫磺残渣
that leave behind sulphuric residue.
恶魔附身
Demonic possession?
这可以解释一个凡人
That would explain how a mortal man
怎么会有力气打开紧急舱门
would've the strength to open up the emergency hatch.
如果他被附身 这就有可能了
If he got possessed, it's possible.
你知道 这超出那些
You know, this goes way beyond
漂浮在床上或呕吐出豌豆汤之类的事情
floating over a bed, or barf from pea soup,
附身在某人身上是一件事
it's one thing to possess a person,
但是利用他去毁掉整架飞机
but to use him to take down an entire airplane?
你之前听说过这样的事情吗
You ever heard something like this before?
从没听过
Never.
我准备好了 开始吧
I'm ready. Let's do this.
感觉怎么样
How are you feeling?
感觉很好
I feel great.
很快你就可以重新驾驶大喷气式飞机啦
You'll be back flying jumbos before you know it.
希望如此
I hope so.
我们飞了多久了
How long we've been up?
大概40分钟
Almost forty minutes.
时间如飞
Wow! The time really does fly.
你在干什么
What are you doing?!
每种宗教 地球上每种文明
So... every religion and every world culture...
都有关于恶魔和附身的概念 是吗
has the concept of demons and demonic possession, right?
例如基督教 印第安人 印度教
Let them christian, native american, hindu,
你随便举一个
you name it.
但是没有一个描述过这类事件
Yeah but not one described anything like this.
不完全是这样的
Well that's not exactly true.
你看 根据小日本的信仰
You see, according japanese believes
灾难是恶魔引起
certain demons are behind some disasters,
自然的或人为的
both natural and man made.
前者造成地震 后者引发疾病
One causes earthquake, and other causes desease.
那么这个导致坠机
And this causes plane crashes?
好吧 那么
All right, so what?
我们有个与时俱进的恶魔
We have a demon that's evolved with the times,
他慢慢学会了占据人身
and found a way to ratchet up the body count?
是的
Yeah.
你知道 在这架飞机之前
And you know, who knows how
谁知道他还使得多少架飞机坠毁
many planes he's brought down before this one.
怎么了
What?
我不知道 我是说这不是常规的闹鬼
I don't know, I mean this is not a normal gig.
我是说 恶魔们无所求
I mean, demons, they don't want anything,
只想随心所欲地造成死亡和破坏
Just death and destruction for their own sake.
这玩大了
This is big.
爸爸在就好了
I wish that dad was here.
我也这么想
Yeah, me too.
- 你好 - 迪恩 我是杰瑞
- Hello? - Dean, it's Jerry.
- 你好 杰瑞 - 我那个驾驶员朋友
- Oh, hi, Jerry. - My pilot friend...
查克·兰博特死了
Chuck Lambert is dead.
杰瑞 我很难过 发生什么了
Jerry, I'm sorry. What happened?
他和他朋友上了架小飞机
He and his buddy went up in a small twin,
但是1小时前飞机坠毁了
but an hour ago the plain went down.
发生在哪
Where this happened?
距这里60英里以西 在拿撒勒
That's 60 miles west of here, in Nazareth.
我试着忽略这里面的讽刺意味
I will try to ignore the irony in that.
什么
Sorry?
没什么
Nothing.
杰瑞 等在那里 我们马上赶到你那里
Jerry, hang on there. I will catch up with you soon.
- 又一起坠机 - 是的
- Another crash? - Yeah.
- 走吧 - 去哪里
- Let's go. - Where?
拿撒勒
Nazareth.
硫磺
Sulphur?
太好了
Oh, that's great.
好吧 两起坠机事件都和查克·兰博特有关
All right, so there're two plane crashes involving Chuck Lambert.
看上去好像恶魔跟着他
This demon sounds like goes after him.
无意冒犯查克
With all respect to Chuck,
要真是这样 这是个好消息
If that's the case, that would be a good news.
那坏消息是什么
What's the bad news?
查克的飞机在起飞40分钟后坠毁
Chuck's plane went down exactly forty minutes on the fly.
看看这个 2485航班也是这样
And get this, so the flight 2485.
40分钟 这意味着什么
40 minutes? What is that mean?
这是圣经上的数字命理
It's biblical numerology.
你知道 诺亚方舟的故事 下了40天雨
You know, Noah's ark, it rained for forty days.
这个数字意味着死亡
That number means death.
我查阅以往的资料 过去10年有6起坠机
I went back and there were six plane crashes over the last decade
都是起飞40分钟后坠毁的
that all went down exactly forty minutes on.
有幸存者吗
Any survivors?
没有 除了最近的那个
No. Or it not until now at least,
2485航班 不知什么原因
until 2485 for some reason.
还记得驾驶室录音里的超自然电子异象说的吗
On the cockpit voice recorder remember what the EVP said?
无人幸存
No survivors.
它在追逐所有的幸存者
It's going after all the survivors.
它要完成任务
It should finish the job.
真的
Really?
谢谢你接受我们的调查
Well, we thank you taking our survey
你若是要坐飞机
and if you do plan a flight
请记得考虑美国不列颠航空公司
Please don't forget your friends at United Britannia Airlines.
谢谢
Thanks.
好的 搞定
All right. That takes
布兰·桑得森和丹尼斯·夏洛威啦
care of Blane Sanderson and Dennis Holloway.
他们最近不会坐飞机
They're not flying any time soon.
那么唯一的线索就是空姐阿曼达·沃克
So the only wild card is the fly attendant, Amanda Walker.
是的 她妹妹卡伦
Right. Her sister Karen
说她的航班晚上8点从明尼阿波利斯市起飞
said her flight leaves in Minneapolis at 8pm,
这是她重回工作岗位的第一晚
That's her first night back on the job.
听起来貌似我们运气不错
It sounds like we just our luck.
迪恩 要开5个小时的车 你不行的
Dean, this is an 5 hour drive, man. Even with you by the wheel.
你干嘛不再打打阿曼达的手机呢
Why don't you call Amanda's cellphone again,
看看我们能否截住她
See if we can head her off the pass.
我已经给她留了3个语音信息了
I already left her three voice messages,
但她关了手机
she just turned her cellphone off.
- 天哪 我们做不到 - 能做到
- God! We never gonna make it. - We'll make it.
那里 30分钟后登机
Right there. It will boarding in thirty minutes.
好的 我们还有机会
Okay, we still left some cards to play.
我们要找个电话
We gonna need find a phone.
机场服务
Airport services.
- 我在13号门 - 您想找谁 先生
- I'm at gate 13. - Who you wanna call, sir?
我想找阿曼达·沃克
I'm trying contact with an Amanda Walker,
她是个空姐 在424航班上
She is a flight attendant on a flight hm... flight 424.
阿曼达·沃克
Amanda Walker.
Amanda Walker,
你有个13号门的白色电话
you have a phone call white call signal from gate 13.
快点
Come on!
我是阿曼达·沃克
This is Amanda Walker.
沃克小姐
Miss Walker?
我是詹姆斯·海德菲尔得医生
Hi, this is Dr. James Hetfield from St.
来自圣弗朗西斯纪念医院
Francis Memorial Hospital.
- 我们有位病人卡伦·沃克 - 我的卡伦
- We have a Karen Walker here. - My Karen?!
情况不是很严重 只是一起小车祸
Nothing serious just a minor car accident,
但她受伤了 所以
But she was injured so...
等下 这不可能 我刚和她通过电话
Wait, wait, that's impossible. I just got off the phone with her.
- 你什么 - 5分钟前
- You what? - Five minutes ago.
她在家 为期末考试填鸭呢
She's at her house cramming for a final...
你是谁
Who is this?
大概搞错了
That's must be some mistake.
你怎么知道我在这里
How would do you even know I was here?
你是文斯的一个朋友
Is this one of Vince's friends?
被你猜中了
Guilties charged.
难以置信
This is unbelievable!
他真的很对不起你
He is really sorry.
你告诉他管好自己
Well, you tell him to mind his own business
离我远点 好吗
and stay out of my life. Okay?
好的 但他今晚很想见你
Yes. But, he really needs to see you tonight.
- 所以 - 不行 对不起 太晚了
- So... - No, I'm sorry, it's too late.
不要这样 拜托
Don't be like that! Come on,
那家伙一团糟 真的好可怜
The guy's a mess, really, a pathetic.
真的
Really?
是的
Oh, yeah!
听着 我得走了 告诉他我落地后打给我
Look, I gotta go... tell him to call me when I landed.
别别 等等 阿曼达 阿曼达
No, no, wait, Amanda... Amanda!
你怎么样
How are you?
- 嘿 鲍勃 - 嘿
- Hey, Bob. - Hey.
该死
Damn it!
就差一点
So close!
好吧 执行B计划
All right, it's time for plan B.
我们登上那架飞机
We're getting on that plane.
等一下
Just hold on a second.
迪恩 那架飞机就要起飞了
Dean, that plane is leaving
机上有100多人
with over a hundred passengers on board,
要是我们的猜想是对的 那架飞机就会坠毁
And if we're right, that plane is gonna crash.
我知道
I know!
好吧 那我们登机
Okay. Then we're getting on that plane,
我们要找到那个恶魔然后驱魔
We need to find that demon and exorcise it.
听着 我去买票
Look, I'll get the tickets,
你尽可能的去捣乱
you just go get whatever you can out of the trunk,
通过安检
Whatever will make it through security,
我们5分钟后这里见
meet me back here in 5 minutes.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
不 一点也不
No, not really.
为什么 怎么啦
Why? What's wrong?
我有点怕
I kind of have this problem with...
坐飞机
Flying?
我现在才发现
It's never been an issue until now.
你开玩笑的吧
Are you joking, right?
你看我像是在开玩笑吗
Do I look like I'm joking?!
你觉得我为什么要开车旅行 萨姆
Why do you think I drive everywhere, Sam?!
好吧 我去
All right. I'll go.
- 什么 - 我自己搞定这事
- What? - I'll do this one my own.
你疯了吗
Are you nuts?!
你自己说过那架飞机会坠毁
You said yourself that's plane gonna crash!
听着 迪恩 要么我们一起 要么我单干
Look, Dean, we can do it together, I can do this one by myself,
没有第三种选择
I'm not seeing a third option here.
拜托
Come on!
真的
Really?
兄弟
Man...
- 你试着放松 - 你试着闭嘴
- Just try to relax. - Just try to shut up!
- 你在哼金属狂热的歌 - 这让我冷静
- Are you humming Metallica? - Calms me down.
听着 兄弟 我知道你紧张
Look, man, I get you're nervous,
但你要集中精神
all right? But you got to stay focused.
好的 我是说 我们还有32分钟
Okay. I mean, we got 32 minutes and counting
找到那个东西 不管它附到谁的身上
to track this thing down or whoever it's possessing anyway
我们要完成驱魔
and perform a full exorcism.
是啊 在拥挤的飞机上会轻松点
Yeah, on a crowded airplane that's gonna be easy.
一步一步来 好吗
Just take one step at a time, all right?
现在 谁被附身了
Now... who is it possessing?
这个 通常是
Well, it's usually gonna be
虚弱的人
somebody with some sort of weakness you know,
这样恶魔才能钻空子
a chink in the armor that the demon can worm through.
吸毒的 有情绪困扰的
Somebody with an addiction, or some sort of emotional distress.
这是坠机后阿曼达第一次飞行
Well this is Amanda's first flight after the crash,
我要是她肯定心中慌乱
if I were her I'd be messed up.
打扰一下 你是阿曼达吗
Excuse me. Are you Amanda?
不 我不是
No, I'm not.
我认错了
Oh, my mistake.
好的 阿曼达肯定会回到那里
All right, well, it's got to
这样我就可以和她说话
be Amanda back there, so I could talk to her.
我要去了解一下她的精神状态
And uh... I'll get a read on her mental state.
要是她已被附身 怎么办
What if she is already possessed?
我方法测试
There is a way to test that.
我带了圣水
I brought holy water.
不行 我想我们要用更可靠的方法
No. I think we can go more settled.
如果她被附身 她会在上帝之名前畏缩
If she's possessed, she'll flinch at the name of God.
好的
Uh, nice.
嘿
Hey?
- 咋啦 - 用拉丁语说
- What? - Say it in Latin.
我知道
I know!
- 又咋啦 - 拉丁语是Christo
- What?! - In latin it's Christo.
伙计 我知道 我不是白痴
Dude, I know! I'm not an idiot!
女士们先生们 这是首次机长讲话
Ladies and gentlemen this is the first officer speak...
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hi. - Hi.
有什么需要帮助的吗
Can I help you in something?
没有 我只是有点晕机
Oh, no. I'm just a bit of an uneasy flier.
到处转转会让我舒服点
Makes me feel better to walk around a little bit.
大家都会这样
Oh, it happens with the best of us.
当然 你作为空姐
Of course, you being a stewardess,
我想坐飞机对你来说很轻松吧
I guess flying comes easy to you.
你会惊讶的
Oh, you'd be surprised.
真的 你坐飞机也紧张
Really? You... you're a nervous flyer?
是的 也许 有点紧张
Yeah, maybe. A little bit.
害怕飞行却在当空姐 你怎么做到的
How is it though being a stewardes you're scared to fly?
说来话长
Kind of a long story.
好吧 不好意思提到这些
All right, I'm sorry for asking.
没关系
Okay.
你从未考虑过其它的职业
You never considered other employment?
没有
No.
听着 每个人都有害怕的东西
Look, everybody scared of something.
我只是 我不会屈服于它
I just... I'm not gonna let it hold me back.
不好意思 你说什么
I'm sorry, did you say something?
我不明白
I didn't... I didn't...
没什么 算了
Oh, nothing, never mind.
好吧
Okay.
好吧 她肯定是
All right, she is gotta be
飞机上状态最好的人
the most well-adjusted person on the planet.
你说了Christo
You said Christo?
- 是的 - 然后
- Yeah. - And?
她没被附身 恶魔不在她身上
There is no demon in her. There is no demon getting in her.
那可能是飞机上的任何人 任何地方
So it is on the plane could be anyone, anywhere.
拜托 这不正常
Come on, that can be normal?!
只是小空气乱流
Hey! Hey... just a little turbulance.
萨姆 这架飞机要坠毁
Sam, this plane is going to crash,
好吧 不要再把我当傻瓜看了
okay? So quit treating me like I'm freaking fool!
- 你要冷静下来 - 对不起 我不行
- You need to calm down. - Well, I'm sorry I can't!
不 你可以的
Yes, you can.
伙计 对自己说肉麻的
Dude, stow the touchy-feely,
自助瑜伽之类废话 没用的
self-help-yoga crap. It's not helping!
听着 你要是恐慌 就容易被恶魔附身
Listen, you're panicked, you're wide open to demonic possession,
所以你要冷静 马上
So you need to calm yourself down, right now.
好
Good.
现在 我找到一个驱魔咒 我觉得会有用
Now, I found an exorcism in here that I think is gonna work.
罗马礼书
The Rituale Romanum.
我们怎么做
What we have to do?
这个为两部分 第一部分
It's two parts. The first
把恶魔从受害者的身体里驱除出去
part is spells the demon from the victim's body
让它显形 这会让它更强大
and makes it manifest which actually makes him more powerful.
- 更强大 - 是的
- More powerful? - Yeah.
为毛
How?
它不再需要附身
Well, it doesn't need to possess someone anymore,
就可以随心所欲的破坏
it can just break out and go on it's own.
为什么那是件好事
Oh, and why is that a good thing?
因为第二部分 把这个混蛋送回地狱
Well, because the second part sends the bastard back to hell.
一劳永逸
Once and for all.
首先 我们要找到它
First things first we gotta find it.
- 伙计 别这样 - 发现什么了
- Man! Don't do that! - Anything?
什么也没有 我们还有多长时间
No, nothing, how much time we got?
15分钟
15 minutes.
也许我们遗漏了某人
Maybe we missed somebody.
也许那个东西不在飞机上
Maybe the thing is just not on the plane.
你这么想
You believe that?
要是你这么想我就这么想
Well, I will, if you will.
怎么啦
What is it?!
她不会相信这个
She is not gonna believe this.
只剩12分钟了 伙计
12 minutes, dude!
嘿
Oh, hi!
希望你不会觉得飞机太颠了
The flight's not too bumpy for you I hope.
实际上 我们要和你谈谈
Actually that's kind of what we need to talk to you about.
好的 有什么可以帮你们的
Okay. What can I do for you?
这听起来很疯狂 但是
This is going to sound nuts, but...
现在我们没时间进行
we just don't have time for
那就是真像 之类的演讲
"The Truth is Out There" Speach right now...
听着 我们知道你在2485航班上
Look, we know you were on the flight 2485.
你们这些人是谁
Who are you guys?
现在 我们和其他的幸存者谈过
Now, we spoken some of the other survivors,
我们知道有些东西使得飞机坠毁
and we know something brought down that plane,
不是机械故障
and it wasn't mechanical failure.
我们需要你的帮助
We need your help,
因为我们要阻止它再次发生 在这里就现在
Because we need to stop from happening again, here, now.
对不起 我很忙 我要回
I'm sorry... I'm very busy, I have to go back...
等等 等一下
Wait, wait a second.
我们不会伤害你
We will not hurt you, okay?
听我说 2485航班驾驶员查克·兰博特
But listen to me. The pilot on 2485, Chuck Lambert,
他死了
he is dead.
什么
What?!
查克死了
Chuck is dead?
他死于坠机
He died in a plane crach.
2个月内2起坠机
And that's two plane crashes in two months.
你不觉得有点奇怪吗
That doesn't strike you a little strange?
听着 2485航班上有些东西不对劲
Look, there was something wrong
也许你感觉到了 也许没有
with 2485 now maybe you sensed it, maybe you didn't,
但这次航班上也有些东西不对劲
But there's something wrong with this flight, too.
阿曼达 你要信我们
Amanda, you have to believe us.
2485航班上有个人
On 2485 there was this man...
他的眼睛
he have this eyes...
是的 这就是我们想说的
Yes, that's exactly what we're talking about!
我不知道你们要我做什么
I don't understand what are you asking me to do?!
去找副驾驶 我们要你把他带过来
Get the co-pilot, we need you to bring him back here.
为什么 他和这个有什么关系
Why? What does he have to do with anything?
我们没时间解释 只要和他谈谈 好吗
We don't have time to explain, we just need to talk to him, okay?
我怎么才能进到驾驶室 叫来副驾驶
How am I supposed to going to the cockpit and get the co-pilot...
尽你所能
Whatever it takes! Do whatever it takes,
告诉他这里有东西坏了
just tell that something's broken back here,
只要把他带出驾驶室 怎么做都行
whatever that'll get him out of that cockpit.
你知道我会因此失去工作
You know that I can lose my job?
要是你不帮我们 你会失去更多
You'll lose lot more than that if you don't help us out!
好吧
Okay.
出了什么问题
Now what's the problem?
等等 你们要把他怎样
Wait, what are you doing with him?
你说过你只想和他谈谈
You said you just wanna talk to him!
我们马上就谈
We are gonna talk to him!
不
No!
天哪 他怎么了
Oh my God! What's wrong with him?
听着 冷静下来
Look, we need you to calm down,
站到帘子外面 不让任何人进来 好吗
we need you outside of the curtain. Don't let anybody in, okay?
你能做到吗
Can you do that?
阿曼达
Amanda?
好的 好的
Okay. Okay.
快点 萨姆 我不知道还能压住他多久
Hurry up, Sam. I don't know how much longer I can hold him.
[咒语]
Regna terrae cantate Deo: psallite Domino...
qui vehitur per caelus, caelos antiquos...
好的 我抓住他了
Okay, I get him!
[咒语]
Ecce, edit vocem suam, vocem potentem Agnoscite potentiam Dei!
我知道你女朋友的事
I know what happened to your girlfriend!
她惨叫着死去
She must have died screaming!
即使是现在 她也在燃烧
Even now, she burns!
萨姆
Sam!
[咒语]
et potentia ejus in nubibus.
我抓着他
I got him!
- 它去哪了 - 飞机里面
- Where it go? - It's on the plane.
快点 我们得解决它
Hurry up! We gotta finish it!
不
Nooo!
[咒语]
Timendus est Deus e sancto suo...
ipse potentiam dat et...
[咒语]
Gloria Patri.
你确定你不能告诉我发生了什么吗
You sure you can't tell me what happened?
我不知道 我在机场工作
I don't know. I was working at the airport,
然后就什么也不知道了
then it all goes blank.
我甚至不知道自己怎么上的飞机
I don't even know how I get on that plane.
还有其它的吗
Anything else?
没了 就这些
No, that's all.
谢谢你们
Thank you.
我们离开这
Let's get out of here.
你还好吧
Are you okay?
迪恩
Dean.
它知道杰西卡
It knew about Jessica.
萨姆 这些东西可以读心 它们撒谎
Sam, these things, they read minds. They lie.
好吗 就是这样
All right? That's all it was.
是的
Yeah.
走吧
Come on.
每人知道你们做了什么 但我知道
Nobody knows what you guys did, but I do.
要不是你们 很多人会死
Lot of people could have been killed.
你们的爸爸一定会以此为傲
Your dad is gonna be real proud.
再见 杰瑞
I'll see you around, Jerry.
- 嘿 杰瑞 - 什么事
- Hey, Jerry! - Yeah?
我想问你 你怎么知道我手机号的
I wanted to ask you, how did you get my cellphone number anyway?
我才用了6个月
I only have it from like six months.
你爸爸给我的
Your dad gave it to me.
- 什么 - 你什么时候和他聊过
- What? - When did you talk to him?
我没有和真的他聊过 但是
Well, I didn't exactly talked to him but...
我打他的手机 他的语言留言让我打你电话
I called his number, his voice message said to give you a call.
再次谢谢 伙计们
Thanks again, guys.
没道理呀 兄弟
This doesn't make any sense, man.
我给爸爸打过50次电话 一直不在服务区
I called dad's number like fifty times. It's been out of service.
我是约翰·温彻斯特 我不能和你联系
This is John Winchester. I can't be reached.
如果有紧急情况 联系我儿子迪恩
If this is an emergency, call my son, Dean.
785- 555- 0179
785-555-0179
他可以帮你
He can help.